Data Availability Statement (DAS)


1. Due to the privacy issue, the original Wi-Fi data is not allowed to be shared. However, the human flow in 3D space is aggregate and thus does not violate the protection of human subjects, or other valid ethical, privacy, or security concerns. 

2. For the generated 3D axial map, due to the security reason, it is not allowed to be shared.

3. For the topological relationship of the network, and the calculated space syntax parameters and some network centralities are shared for regression analysis. 


